[{"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["2", "+", "9", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [11, 8, 1, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["3", "+", "8", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [11, 7, 1, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["3", "+", "9", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 7, 2, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["4", "+", "7", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [11, 6, 1, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["4", "+", "8", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 6, 2, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["4", "+", "9", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 6, 3, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["5", "+", "6", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [11, 5, 1, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["5", "+", "7", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 5, 2, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["5", "+", "8", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 5, 3, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["5", "+", "9", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 5, 4, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["6", "+", "5", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [11, 4, 1, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["6", "+", "6", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 4, 2, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["6", "+", "7", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 4, 3, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["6", "+", "8", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 4, 4, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["6", "+", "9", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 4, 5, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["7", "+", "4", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [11, 3, 1, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["7", "+", "5", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 3, 2, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["7", "+", "6", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 3, 3, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["7", "+", "7", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 3, 4, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["7", "+", "8", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 3, 5, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["7", "+", "9", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [16, 3, 6, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["8", "+", "3", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [11, 2, 1, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["8", "+", "4", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 2, 2, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["8", "+", "5", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 2, 3, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["8", "+", "6", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 2, 4, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["8", "+", "7", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 2, 5, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["8", "+", "8", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [16, 2, 6, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["8", "+", "9", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [17, 2, 7, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["9", "+", "2", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [11, 1, 1, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["9", "+", "3", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 1, 2, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["9", "+", "4", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 1, 3, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["9", "+", "5", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 1, 4, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["9", "+", "6", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 1, 5, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["9", "+", "7", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [16, 1, 6, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["9", "+", "8", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [17, 1, 7, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "算一算，填一填", "stem": "算一算，填一填", "type": "au-num-deciliter", "content": ["9", "+", "9", "=", ""]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [18, 1, 8, 10], "knowledges": ["20以内数的进位加法"], "number": "1-7-8-01"}]